http://www.artexlabel.com/privacy-policy/

The Label Pros
Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ)
News
Pressure Sensitive Label Printing, Label Manufacturing, Custom Stickers » Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy Summary
Because we want to build users’ trust and confidence in our company and demonstrate our commitment to privacy, we want to disclose our privacy practices. Your privacy is very important to us. As part of our normal operation, we collect information about you. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect about you and how this information is used.
Information
We do not sell, rent, distribute or provide your personal or corporate information to third parties. We collect the domain name and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our web site, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our web site and used to notify consumers about updates to our web site.
Cookies
We use cookies to record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, customize web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends.
Other Parties
This Privacy Policy only addresses the use of information and its disclosure by us. We do not control the privacy policies of any third parties. If you choose to disclose information to other parties, we recommend that you ask them about their privacy policies prior to your disclosure.
Security
We use industry-standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information. We also employ firewalls and user authentication to ensure your information is protected.
Updates to This Policy
We may update or amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Policy to our web site. We encourage you to review this Policy from time to time.
Artex Label & Graphics
We provide custom labels for pharmaceuticals, food and beverages, cleaning products, educational products, promotional stickers and more. Contact us get started >>
©2013-2016 Artex Label & Graphics, Inc.
©2013-2016 Artex Label & Graphics, Inc.
Privacy Policy
Sitemap
Contact Us
